A Guide to Records of the Secretary of Finance, 1998-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)
Library of Virginia
- Department of Taxation-Real Property Nominal Tax Rate, 2006. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Revenue Forecasting. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Revenue Impact of Fed. Leg., 2006. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Service Awards. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-State and Local Online Lodging Taxes. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Streamlined Sales and Use Tax Agreement. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Governor's Briefing-Tax Return Backlogs. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Unemployment Tax Filing. (Box 24)
- Department of Taxation-Summary of VA Tax Structure. (Box 24)
- Tax Adjustments. (Box 24)
- Tax - To Be Filed. (Box 24)
- US Executive Summary. (Box 24)
- Tax-HR Complaint-Willie Brailey. (Box 24)
- Tax-Mr. Busch. (Box 24)
- Tax-Collections Proposals. (Box 24)
- HB 3202. (Box 25)
- Jameron Letter. (Box 25)
- VETO Case Law. (Box 25)
- Veto. (Box 25)
- Timing. (Box 25)
- Shutdown. (Box 25)
- Veto of Language in Budget Bill. (Box 25)
- Veto?? (Box 25)
- University Budget Cuts. (Box 25)
- Walking Around Lists. (Box 25)
- Secretary of Finance, Feb. 2008 (Box 25)
- Approved Concerns with 2008 Session House and Senate Budget Actions. (Box 25)
- Conferee Letter, Feb. 2008 (Box 25)
- Casey Foundation Report. (Box 25)
- Budget, 2008. (Box 25)
- Budget Reduction Work. (Box 25)
- Budget, FY07. (Box 25)
- Bills and Budget, 2006. (Box 25)
- Continuity of Operations, 2006. (Box 25)
- Goal 11 Performance Measures. (Box 25)
- Correspondence and Documents, 2006. (Box 25)
- Correspondence etc., 2007. (Box 25)
- SCHEV. (Box 25)
- Prefiling Legislation. (Box 25)
- Budget Meetings. (Box 25)
- Carry Forwards, 2007. (Box 25)
- Budget Reduction Plan. (Box 25)
- Working Papers Gov's Amends. to HB 5002. (Box 25)
- HB 3202. (Box 25)
- Transportation Package (Box 25)
- Agency Proposed Budget Reduction Strategies. (Box 25)
- House Appro., Oct. 2006. (Box 26)
- House Approrpiations Committee re: August Rev., Sep. 2007. (Box 26)
- Revenue Letter, Jan. 2006. (Box 26)
- Revenue Letter, Feb. 2006. (Box 26)
- Revenue Letter with Extra Attachment, Feb. 2006. (Box 26)
- Revenue Letter, Mar. 2006. (Box 26)
- Revenue Letter, Apr. 2006. (Box 26)
- Revenue Letter, May 2006. (Box 26)
- Revenue Letter, Aug. 2006. (Box 26)
- Revenue Letter, Sep. 2006. (Box 26)
- HAC/SFC Presentation Sep. Rev. (Box 26)
- Revenue Letter, Oct. 2006. (Box 26)
- Revenue Letter, Nov. 2006. (Box 26)
- Revenue Letter, Dec. 2006. (Box 26)
- Revenue Letter, Jan. 2007. (Box 26)
- Revenue Letter, Feb. 2007. (Box 26)
- Revenue Letter, Mar. 2007. (Box 26)
- Revenue Letter, May 2007. (Box 26)
- Senate Fin. Comm., June 2007. (Box 26)
- Revenue Letter, Aug. 2007. (Box 26)
- Revenue Report, Sep. 2007. (Box 26)
- Joint Money Committee Meeting, Dec. 2004. (Box 26)
- Joint Money Committee Meeting, Aug. 2004. (Box 26)
- House Appropriations Revenue Presentation, Apr. 2006. (Box 26)
- House Appropriations Committee Joint Meeting, Aug. 2007. (Box 26)
- Presentations. (Box 26)
- Joint Money Committee. (Box 26)
- Rating Agency Presentations, 2007. (Box 26)
- Budget, FY2008. (Box 26)
- Presentation, Aug. 2007. (Box 26)
- Rating Agency Visit, 2007. (Box 26)
- Agenda. (Box 26)
- Jamestown Visitors Center. (Box 26)
- Place Cards. (Box 26)
- Dinner at VMFA, June 2007. (Box 26)
- Bond Presentations, June 2007. (Box 26)
- HJR 147 G.A. Revenue Estimates. (Box 26)
- Revenue Reports. (Box 26)
- Forecasting Improvements. (Box 26)
- Rev. Collections, FY2006. (Box 26)
- December Revenues, 2005. (Box 26)
- Rev. Forecasting-General, 2004. (Box 26)
- Governor's Advisory Board of Economists (GABE), 2006. (Box 27)
- GABE, 2006. (Box 27)
- GACRE, Nov. 2007 (Box 27)
- GACRE, July 25, 2007. (Box 27)
- GACRE, July 2007. (Box 27)
- GACRE, Nov. 2005. (Box 27)
- GACRE, Nov. 2004. (Box 27)
- GACRE, 2008. (Box 27)
- Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast Through FY2010, 2017. (Box 27)
- GABE, Feb. 2008. (Box 27)
- GACRE, Nov. 2007. (Box 27)
- GACRE. (Box 27)
- Dec. Revenue Letter and Senate Slides. (Box 27)
- GACRE, Feb. 2008. (Box 27)
- Presentations etc., 2003-2005. (Box 27)
- Senate Finance Retreat, Nov. 2007. (Box 27)
- TICR Meeting, Jan. 2007. (Box 28)
- TICR Meeting, Nov. 2006. (Box 28)
- TICR Meeting, July 2006. (Box 28)
- TICR Meeting, Apr. 2006. (Box 28)
- Special Projects, Apr. 2006. (Box 28)
- TICR-Long Range Planning Committee, Nov. 2006. (Box 28)
- TICR-Long Range Planning Committee, Oct. 2006. (Box 28)
- TICR-Master Settlement Agreement (MSA) Payments. (Box 28)
- TICR-Proposed Megasites: Southside Va Locations, Dec. 2006. (Box 28)
- TICR-Spec. Proj. Committee. (Box 28)
- TICR-Special Projects Meeting, Apr. 2006. (Box 28)
- TICR-Special Projects Applications, Apr. 2006. (Box 28)
- Tobacco Financing Corporation Board - Appointments. (Box 28)
- Tobacco Financing Corporation Board - Refinancing Opportunities. (Box 28)
- Tobacco Commission. (Box 28)
- Tobacco. (Box 28)
- Tobacco Settlement Financing Corporation, Presentation, July 2006. (Box 28)
- Tobacco Commission, July-Aug. 2006. (Box 28)
- TICR Roundtable, 2008. (Box 28)
- TICR Roundtable. (Box 28)
- TICR Draft Memo. (Box 28)
- Tobacco Comm. (Box 28)
- TICR-Long Range Planning Committee. (Box 28)
- Virginia Tobacco Commission, July 2008. (Box 28)
- Wallops Island. (Box 29)
- Capital Improvement Planning and Funding, 2008 Session. (Box 29)
- Governor's Transportation Bill. (Box 29)
- Va. Beach Sheriff VIP Assigned to PS. (Box 29)
- NVTA/HRTA, 2008. (Box 29)
- HB 1547. (Box 29)
- Admin. (Box 29)
- Ballard. (Box 29)
- Outlying Landing Field, Feb. 2008. (Box 29)
- OLF Meeting. (Box 29)
- C Preparedness. (Box 29)
- Commerce and Trade. (Box 29)
- SCHEV (State Council of Higher Education for Virginia). (Box 29)
- HHR. (Box 29)
- NR. (Box 29)
- Land Preservation. (Box 29)
- Dept. of Veterans Affairs. (Box 29)
- HB 570 - PS. (Box 29)
- Public Safety. (Box 29)
- House and Senate Democrats Numbers. (Box 29)
- Technology. (Box 29)
- Productivity Investment Fund. (Box 29)
- Productivity Investment Fund, Round 2 Grant Submissions. (Box 29)
- Transportation. (Box 29)
- Virginia Port Authority. (Box 29)
- Workforce. (Box 29)
- DCAC, Feb. 2008. (Box 30)
- Virginia Tobacco Indemnifiction and Community Revitalization Commission. (Box 30)
- Boards. (Box 30)
- Immigration Commission. (Box 30)
- FADFM-Secretary Jody M. Wagner. (Box 30)
- FMFADA Meeting, Mar. 2008. (Box 30)
- Secretary Jody M. Wagner-FMFADA. (Box 30)
- FADA. (Box 30)
- FADA Meeting. (Box 30)
- FMFADA Meeting, Bay Breeze Comm. Center. (Box 30)
- Secretary Jody M. Wagner-FMFADA Board Meetings. (Box 30)
- Fort Monroe Reuse Program. (Box 30)
- Secretary Jody M. Wagner-FMFADA Board Meetings, May 2008. (Box 30)
- Secretary Jody M. Wagner-FMFADA Board Meetings, July 2008. (Box 30)
- VEDP. (Box 30)
- VEDP Board Meeting, June 2008. (Box 30)
- VEDP Draft Operating Plan. (Box 30)
- VEAP. (Box 30)
- Southwest Economic Development Committee. (Box 30)
- Virginia Tourism Board, Chincoteague Island. (Box 30)
- Virginia Tourism Authority Annual Financial Statements. (Box 30)
- VDEP Proposed Operating Plan. (Box 30)
- Tobacco Indemnifiction and Community Revitalization Endowment. (Box 30)
- VTIC-Special Projects Committee Meeting, July 2008. (Box 30)
- TICR Meeting, July 2007. (Box 30)
- TICR Meeting, May 2007. (Box 30)
- TICR Meeting, Apr. 2007. (Box 30)
- Completed Decision Briefs. (Box 31)
- Decision Briefs, 2008. (Box 31)
- Decision Briefs, 2007. (Box 31)
- Completed Bond Packages. (Box 31)
- Bond Packages, 2008. (Box 31)
- Bond Package-Series 2008A. (Box 31)
- Bond Packages, 2009. (Box 31)
- Secretary of Administration Decision Briefs. (Box 31)
- Agriculture and Forestry. (Box 31)
- Secretary of the Commonwealth Decision Briefs. (Box 31)
- Commonwealth Preparedness. (Box 31)
- Secretary of Education Decision Briefs. (Box 31)
- Secretary of Commerce and Trade Decision Briefs. (Box 31)
- Sec. of Health and Human Resources Decision Briefs. (Box 31)
- Secretary of Finance Decision Briefs. (Box 31)
- Productivity Investment Fund. (Box 32)
- Secretary of Transportation Decision Briefs. (Box 32)
- Secretary of Natural Resources Decision Briefs. (Box 32)
- Secretary of Public Safety Decision Briefs. (Box 32)
- Secretary of Technology Decision Briefs. (Box 32)
- Workforce Decision Briefs. (Box 32)
- Escheats, 2007. (Box 32)
- Escheats, 2006. (Box 32)
- Metropolitan Washington Airpots Authority, 2007. (Box 32)
- Eastern Virginia Medical School, 2007. (Box 32)
- 9C Bond Bill Higher Ed. Capital Projects, 2007. (Box 32)
- General Obligation Refunding Bonds, 2007. (Box 32)
- VA College Building Auth. Bonds, 2007. (Box 32)
- VA Housing Development Auth. Bonds, 2007. (Box 32)
- VA Housing Development Auth.: Single-Family Housing Bonds, 2007. (Box 32)
- VA Port Authority Bond, 2007. (Box 32)
- VA Public Building Auth. Public Facilities Revenue Bonds, 2007. (Box 32)
- VA Small Business Financing Auth. Bonds, 2007. (Box 32)
- UVA Commercial Paper Program, 2007. (Box 32)
- Transportation, 2007. (Box 32)
- 9C Bond Bill JMU/TECH Project Bonds, 2006 (Box 32)
- General Obligation Refunding Bonds Series 2006A, 2006. (Box 32)
- General Obligation Refunding Bonds, 2006. (Box 32)
- VA College Building Auth. Bonds, 2006. (Box 32)
- VCU GO Pledge Bonds $75,000,000, 2006. (Box 32)
- VHDA $211,002,185 Tax-Exempt Rental Housing Bonds, 2006. (Box 32)
- VA Housing Development Auth. Bonds, 2006. (Box 32)
- VA Development Aut.: Single-Family Housing Bonds, 2006. (Box 32)
- VCBA $53,835,000 Educational Facilities Revenue Bonds, 2006. (Box 32)
- VA Port Authority Bond, 2006. (Box 32)
- VA Public Building Auth. Public Facilities Revenue Bonds, 2006. (Box 32)
- VA Small Business Financing Auth. Bonds., 2006. (Box 32)
- Decision Briefs. (Box 32)
- Decision Brief-Ballard Property in Norfolk, VA. (Box 32)
- Escheats. (Box 33)
- Bonds. (Box 33)
- Commonwealth Transportation Board. (Box 33)
- 9C Higher Educational Institutions Bond Issuance Bill. (Box 33)
- Eastern Virginia Medical School. (Box 33)
- General Obligation Boards (Box 33)
- Metropolitan Washington Airports Authority Bonds (MWAA). (Box 33)
- George Mason University. (Box 33)
- James Madison University. (Box 33)
- Tobacco Settlement Financing Corporation. (Box 33)
- Virginia Aviation Board. (Box 33)
- Commonwealth Transportation Board. (Box 33)
- Medical College of Hampton Roads. (Box 33)
- Virginia Biotechnology Research Park. (Box 33)
- University of Virginia. (Box 33)
- Virginia Tech. (Box 33)
- Virginia College Building Authority. (Box 33)
- Commerce and Trade. (Box 33)
- Virginia Commonwealth University. (Box 33)
- VPI and SU. (Box 33)
- Virginia Housing Development Authority. (Box 33)
- Secretary of the Commonwealth. (Box 33)
- Health and Human Resources. (Box 33)
- Public Safety. (Box 33)
- Administration. (Box 33)
- Education. (Box 33)
- Finance. (Box 33)
- Natural Resources. (Box 33)
- Transportation. (Box 33)
- Technology. (Box 33)
- Hiring Requests. (Box 33)
- Accounts. (Box 33)
- Planning and Budget. (Box 33)
- State Internal Auditor. (Box 33)
- Taxation. (Box 33)
- Treasury. (Box 33)
- Virginia Port Authority. (Box 33)
- Virginia Public Building Authority. (Box 33)
- Virginia Public School Authority. (Box 33)
- Virginia Resources Authority. (Box 33)
- Virginia Small Business Financing Authority. (Box 33)
- FY2009. (Box 34)
- Presentation for the Norfolk and Portsmouth Bar Association, Feb. 2008. (Box 34)
- Presentation for the 2008 Governor's Fellows, July 2008. (Box 34)
- Lead VA, Apr. 2006. (Box 34)
- Present. to Cabinet, June 2007. (Box 34)
- Governor's Fellows, July 2007. (Box 34)
- Gov. Agency HD Meeting, May 2007. (Box 34)
- August Rev. Data. (Box 34)
- Joint Finance Committee, Aug. 2006. (Box 34)
- JLARC Report, Aug. 2006. (Box 34)
- Actual General Fund Revenues, FY2006. (Box 34)
- Sorenson Institute Speech, June 2007. (Box 34)
- LEAD VIRGINIA. (Box 34)
- Petersburg Town Hall. (Box 34)
- Delegate Dance Town Hall. (Box 34)
- Virginia Tobacco Commission. (Box 34)
- FOCOS @ Longwood, Nov. 2007. (Box 34)
- VA Business Council, Nov. 2007. (Box 34)
- VA Beach Vision, Nov. 2007. (Box 34)
- United Way. (Box 34)
- VEI. (Box 34)
- Warner Speech. (Box 34)
- Leadership Speech, Apr. 2007. (Box 34)
- Central Virginia Business District Association, Apr. 2007. (Box 34)
- VA Municipal League, Oct. 2006. (Box 34)
- Speech, Cape Henry, Apr. 2007. (Box 34)
- Central VA Healthcare Executive Group, Mar. 2007. (Box 34)
- SFC, Oct. 2007. (Box 34)
- HAC. (Box 34)
- Presentation to VAFREE-Candidate Interview Forum. (Box 34)
- HAC. (Box 34)
- Understanding Virginia's Budget-Presentation for Lead Virginia, 2006. (Box 34)
- Six-Year Improvement Program, FY 2007-2012. (Box 34)
- Senate Finances, May 2007. (Box 34)
- VA Assessing Officers. (Box 34)
- Virginia's Planning and Budget System-Presentation for Sorenson Institute, 2006. (Box 34)
- NuSolutions. (Box 34)
- Cabinet. (Box 34)
- Gov. Cabinet, Sep. 2006. (Box 34)
- Traveling Cabinet. (Box 34)
- Sorenson, June 2006. (Box 34)
- VEI, June 2006. (Box 34)
- Lenders Forum, June 2006. (Box 34)
- VA State University, June 2006. (Box 34)
- Hampton Roads Tax Forum, May 2006. (Box 34)
- Hadassah, May 2006. (Box 34)
- Sorensen Presentation, Apr. 2006. (Box 34)
- Budget Process Powerpoint. (Box 34)
- Presentation, Feb. 2006. (Box 34)
- Presentation to Norfolk and Portsmouth Bar Association. (Box 34)
- Presentation for Thomas Jefferson Group. (Box 34)
- Hampton Roads Chamber of Commerce Regional Board of Directors/Trustees, Jan. 2008. (Box 34)
- Sorenson Leaders Program. (Box 34)
- Norfolk Foundation. (Box 34)
- L'Anson-Hoffman Inn of Court. (Box 34)
- Community Integration Advisory Board. (Box 34)
- Senate Finance Committee, SOF Presentation, Jan. 2006. (Box 34)
- Senate Presentation, Mar. 2006. (Box 34)
- SB 5011. (Box 34)
- Presentation to House Finance Comm., Jan. 2006. (Box 34)
- Mid-Session Revenue Forecast Talking Points. (Box 34)
- House Appropriation Committee, Jan. 2006. (Box 34)
- Medicaid Issues, 2006. (Box 35)
- Decentralization and VPPA, 2006-2008. (Box 35)
- Governor Tabletop Exercise, 2008. (Box 35)
- Miner Act, 2006. (Box 35)
- DMAS-Budget, 2008-2010 (Box 35)
- Enterprise Applications Project, 2005-2006. (Box 35)
- VA Lottery Overview, 2008. (Box 35)
- General Fund Forecast, 2006. (Box 35)
- Advisory Committee Mega Projects, 2007. (Box 35)
- Medicaid Forecast Budget, 2008. (Box 35)
- JMU Six-Year Plan, 2008-2014. (Box 35)
- Sales and Use Tax-Telecom Exemption, Sep 2006. (Box 35)
- Independence Day Invitation Response. (Box 35)
- Collection Non Debt CGI Pres., Aug. 2008. (Box 35)
- SCHEV Higher Ed Strategic Plan, 2007-2013. (Box 35)
- Medicaid Monthly Expenditure Reports, Jan. 2006-2008. (Box 35)
- Spaceport/Orbitel. (Box 35)
- 05 Rating Agency Pres. (Box 35)
- Axon Financial-Security Lending, Dec. 2007. (Box 35)
- Dept. of Accounts. (Box 35)
- VA First Cities Coalition, Oct. 2005. (Box 35)
- Budget Scenarios, May 2006. (Box 35)
- Agency Strategic Plans Final Version, 2006. (Box 35)
- Revenue Stabilization Fund. (Box 35)
- Tobacco Settlement. (Box 35)
- Finance Legislative Proposals, 2008. (Box 35)
- Medicaid Expenditures, 2006-2007. (Box 35)
- Budget Update DBP, Sep. 2007. (Box 35)
- Dept. of Treasury Strategic Plan, 2006. (Box 35)
- EA, 2007. (Box 35)
- EA Master Service Agreement, 2006. (Box 35)
- Budget Overview, 2006 Session. (Box 36)
- Debt Capacity Advisory Committee, Dec. 2006. (Box 36)
- GABE Meeting, Oct. 2006. (Box 36)
- Secretary Transportation Budget, 2007 Session. (Box 36)
- HHR Budget, 2007 Session. (Box 36)
- FIN Budget Priorities, 2007 Session. (Box 36)
- Executive Amendments, 2007 Session. (Box 36)
- Tax Rankings, 2007. (Box 36)
- Governor's Performance Leadership Forum, Apr. 2006. (Box 36)
- DMAS-DSH Payments-OIG Audit Report, 2006. (Box 36)
- NR-Biofuels, 2007. (Box 36)
- Budget, 2007 Session. (Box 36)
- Governor's Tax Initiatives, 2007 Session. (Box 36)
- Dahlgren Education and Research Institute, 2007. (Box 36)
- Higher Ed., 2007 Session. (Box 36)
- TICR-Financing Strategies. (Box 36)
- HHR Initiatives, 2007. (Box 36)
- WQIF, 2007. (Box 36)
- Sudan Divestments, 2007. (Box 36)
- Revenue Data, Dec. 2007. (Box 36)
- DOA-ARMICS Budget, 2007. (Box 36)
- Tobacco MSA Deposits, FY06-07, FY07-08. (Box 36)
- OPEB. (Box 36)
- Administration Budget Requests, 2007. (Box 36)
- Ag. and Forestry Budget Requests, 2007. (Box 36)
- Commerce and Trade Budget Requests, 2007. (Box 36)
- Budget Conferences Letter, 2007. (Box 36)
- Budget Meeting with Secretaries. (Box 36)
- Natural Resources Budget Requests, 2007. (Box 36)
- Health and Human Res. Budget Requests, 2007. (Box 36)
- Budget Growth Statistics. (Box 36)
- Commonwealth Preparedness Budget Requests, 2007. (Box 36)
- Commonwealth Budget Requests, 2007. (Box 36)
- Education Budget Requests, 2007. (Box 36)
- Budget Reduction Under Wilder, 1990. (Box 36)
- Technology Budget Requests, 2007. (Box 36)
- Transportation Budget Requests, 2007. (Box 36)
- Workforce Budget Requests, 2007. (Box 36)
- Public Safety Budget Requests, 2007. (Box 36)
- Finance Budget Requests, 2007. (Box 36)
- Six-Year Plan. (Box 36)
- Economic Impact Analysis of Gov's Higher Ed. Bond Bill. (Box 36)
- Focus, 2008. (Box 37)
- CT Report-Consolidation DBA and VEPP, Oct. 2008. (Box 37)
- Medicaid Cost Recovery-CGI, June 2007. (Box 37)
- CGI-Medicaid Recoveries, 2008. (Box 37)
- Medicaid Forecast, Nov. 2008. (Box 37)
- UVA Six-Year Plan, 2008. (Box 37)
- Monthly Revenue Letter (JMW). (Box 37)
- Preliminary Reviews, Mar. 2008. (Box 37)
- Finance-Resumes. (Box 37)
- OPEB, 2006. (Box 37)
- OPEB, Feb. 2008. (Box 37)
- OPEB, 2006. (Box 37)
- Congressional Briefing Papers, 2007. (Box 37)
- Congressional Briefing Papers, 2008. (Box 37)
- SOF-Office Info. (Box 37)
- Health Care Fund. (Box 37)
- VITA/NG Partnership Issues. (Box 37)
- Capital Bond Structure, 2008. (Box 37)
- Business Activity Tax, 2008. (Box 37)
- Korpe Meeting, July 2008. (Box 37)
- Performance Building RFP, Jan. 2008. (Box 37)
- Performance Budgeting, 2008-2010. (Box 37)
- Memo to Agencies re: Budget Savings, Feb. 2008. (Box 37)
- PPTRA. (Box 37)
- SOF Events Calendar. (Box 37)
- Interest Forecasting Model. (Box 37)
- Revenue Status Briefing, May 2007. (Box 37)
- Senate Finance Committee-Revenue Update. (Box 37)
- Electronic Payment and Collections, May 2008. (Box 37)
- Energy Efficient Appliances TAX and DMME. (Box 37)
- Car Tax, 2006. (Box 37)
- Letter to Stosch, Feb. 2008. (Box 37)
- State Contracts-Collections, 2008. (Box 37)
- Money Committee Presentations, 2008. (Box 37)
- Monthly Revenue Reports (DOA), 2008. (Box 37)
- HB 5001, 2008. (Box 37)
- Commonwealth Debt-Overview to SFC, Jan. 2008. (Box 37)
- Meeting w/ TRS, July 2008. (Box 37)
- HB/SB 30. (Box 37)
- Budget Highlights, 2008. (Box 37)
- Governor's Early Childhood Initiatives. (Box 37)
- Governor Vetoes. (Box 37)
- Governor's Speech, 2008. (Box 37)
- Management Scorecard, 2008. (Box 37)
- Infrastructure Privatization, Chicago, Sep. 2006. (Box 37)
- Potomac Edison-Bond Securitization. (Box 37)
- Deputy Meeting, 2008. (Box 37)
- FOIA Council, 2007. (Box 37)
- DGS-eVA Rebate Fees to Higher Ed Institutions, May 2008. (Box 37)
- VEDP-Operating Plan, FY09. (Box 37)
- Northrup Grunman-Transfer of VA Advanced Shipbuilding and Carrier Integration Center. (Box 37)
- TILR Strategic Plan, 2006. (Box 37)
- Potential Economic Development Project. (Box 37)
- Virginia Employment Commission. (Box 37)
- TAX and VED Major IT Project. (Box 37)
- VRA, July 2007. (Box 37)
- TICR Meeting, June 2008. (Box 37)
- Mega Projects, 2007. (Box 37)
- SRI. (Box 37)
- VA Space Flight Academy-Aerospace Advisory Council, 2008. (Box 37)
- Orbital Sciences. (Box 37)
- SRI. (Box 37)
- SRI Funding (Local Budget Letters). (Box 37)
- SRI-Report for the First Quarter, 2008. (Box 37)
- BAR Report-H/S Budget Actions, 2008. (Box 37)
- COS Letter to Agencies re: GF Revenues, July 2008. (Box 37)
- DOA Revenue Reports, 2008. (Box 37)
- DOA-MCI Reports, 2008. (Box 37)
- Bond-Crow's Nest, Apr. 2008. (Box 37)
- Bearing Point-Overview, June 2008. (Box 37)
- Rainy Day Fund. (Box 37)
- Jefferson Lab/SURA, 2008 (Box 37)
- Misc. SOE SWAM, 2008. (Box 37)
- Virginia's P-16 Education Council. (Box 37)
- Auxiliary Interest Yield and Auxiliary Indirect Cost Recovery, 2006-2010. (Box 37)
- Tuition Moderation Fund, 2008. (Box 37)
- Virginia Lottery Meeting on HR Issues. (Box 38)
- Virginia Lottery-Secretary Wagner. (Box 38)
- Reductions and Budget Development Docs, 2008-2010. (Box 38)
- Approved Agency Budget Reduction Strategies, 2008. (Box 38)
- Budget Reductons. (Box 38)
- Tax Budget Reductions FY09/FY10, 2008. (Box 38)
- VHDA-Update to HFC, Aug. 2008. (Box 38)
- Tax Policy Changes. (Box 38)
- DMAS-CMS Proposal, Apr. 2008. (Box 38)
- Consensus Medicaid Forecast, FY07-08. (Box 38)
- SWAM Procurement. (Box 38)
- 599 Formula Study Meeting, May 2006. (Box 38)
- Local Health Department Closures. (Box 38)
- VEAP Briefing to the Secretary of Finance. (Box 38)
- Secretary of Agricultue and Forestry. (Box 39)
- Current Medicaid Trends DMAS, Sep. 2007. (Box 39)
- Education: Blue Ridge Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Central Virginia Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Dabney S. Lancaster Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Danville Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Eastern Shore Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Germanna Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: John Tyler Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Lord Fairfax Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Mountain Empire Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: New River Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Northern Virginia Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Patrick Henry Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Paul D. Camp Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Piedmont Virginia Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Rappahannock Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Richard Bland College. (Box 39)
- Education: Southside Virginia Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Southwest Virginia Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Thomas Nelson Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Tidewater Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Virginia Community College System (Facilities Management Services). (Box 39)
- Education: Virginia Community College System (System Office). (Box 39)
- Education: Virginia Highlands Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Western Community Community College. (Box 39)
- Education: Wytheville Community College. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Commerce and Trade (Box 39)
- Secretary of Commerce and Trade: Mega Projects Legislation. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Commerce and Trade: Tourism. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Commerce and Trade: VEDP. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Commerce and Trade: VEC-Restructuring Plan. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Commerce and Trade: VEC-Downsizing. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Administration: Employee Compensation. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Administration: DGS. (Box 39)
- Budget/Track Meetings. (Box 39)
- General Fund Track. (Box 39)
- Business Meeting-Agendas. (Box 39)
- Issues to Be Discussed with Governor. (Box 39)
- Reallocation List. (Box 39)
- Governor's Comments. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Health and Human Resources: DPB Secretarial Prioritizaiton, 2008. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Health and Human Resources: HHR Budget Packages. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Health and Human Resources: VA Share. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Health and Human Resources: MHMR. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Health and Human Resources: DMAS. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Health and Human Resources: HHR-McKinsey Report. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health and Human Resources. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Finance: OPEB. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Finance: Debt Capacity. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Finance: NGF Interest. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Finance: FY07 Reappropriation. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Finance: Finance-At-Wills (Box 39)